[
    {
        "ID": "1",
        "Question": "Famous artist Pablo Picasso belongs to which country?",
        "AnswerA": "Spain",
        "AnswerB": "Italy",
        "AnswerC": "France",
        "AnswerD": "Portugal",
        "CorrectAnswer": "A"
    },
    {
        "ID": "2",
        "Question": "Leonardo da Vinci was one of the leading artists of the High Renaissance, from which country?",
        "AnswerA": "Spain",
        "AnswerB": "Ireland",
        "AnswerC": "Portugal",
        "AnswerD": "Italy",
        "CorrectAnswer": "D"
    },
    {
        "ID": "3",
        "Question": "Which animal is treated the cleanest?",
        "AnswerA": "Whale",
        "AnswerB": "Pigs",
        "AnswerC": "Giraffe",
        "AnswerD": "Zebra",
        "CorrectAnswer": "B"
    },
    {
        "ID": "4",
        "Question": "What is the rarest bug in the world?",
        "AnswerA": "Panda ant",
        "AnswerB": "Title Beetle",
        "AnswerC": "Land/ Tree lobster",
        "AnswerD": "Karner butterfly",
        "CorrectAnswer": "C"
    },
    {
        "ID": "5",
        "Question": "What is the hardest sport in the world?",
        "AnswerA": "Karate",
        "AnswerB": "Water Polo",
        "AnswerC": "Weight Lifting",
        "AnswerD": "Archery",
        "CorrectAnswer": "B"
    },
    {
        "ID": "6",
        "Question": "What is the oldest sport?",
        "AnswerA": "Wrestling",
        "AnswerB": "Kabadi",
        "AnswerC": "Bull Fight",
        "AnswerD": "Cockfight",
        "CorrectAnswer": "A"
    },
    {
        "ID": "7",
        "Question": "What animal is lazy?",
        "AnswerA": "Tree weta",
        "AnswerB": "The panda ant",
        "AnswerC": "Red-fanged funnel spider",
        "AnswerD": "Sloths",
        "CorrectAnswer": "D"
    },
    {
        "ID": "8",
        "Question": "What is the world’s heaviest insect?",
        "AnswerA": "Stresemann’s Bristlefront",
        "AnswerB": "Dryococelus australis",
        "AnswerC": "Land lobster",
        "AnswerD": "Tree weta",
        "CorrectAnswer": "C"
    },
    {
        "ID": "9",
        "Question": "Which footballer has won the most trophies?",
        "AnswerA": "Vitor Bala",
        "AnswerB": "Ryan Giggs ",
        "AnswerC": "Dani Alves",
        "AnswerD": "Wael Gomaa",
        "CorrectAnswer": "C"
    },
    {
        "ID": "10",
        "Question": " Which player has the most Champions League?",
        "AnswerA": "Paolo Maldini (AC Milan)",
        "AnswerB": "Francisco Gento (Real Madrid)",
        "AnswerC": "Alessandro Costacurta (AC Milan)",
        "AnswerD": "Cristiano Ronaldo (Manchester United, Real Madrid)",
        "CorrectAnswer": " B"
    }
]